"Psychics"
"Mobgle Search"
"Psychics" "Mobgle Search" The Spirits and
Such Consultation Office's official homepage...
The Spirits and Such Consultation
Office's official homepage...
"Spiritual power-Mobpedian" "100 ways to tell if a psychic is real or not" " A psychic's advice
to those living with the gift" The Spirits and Such Consultation Office's official homepage...
The Spirits and Such Consultation
Office's official homepage...
“"[Psychics] Spirits and Such Consultation Office Homepage: Reigen Arataka [Exorcisms & Séances]” "Psychic Jet I A relaxing spiritual life I
Seasoning City Center” "Let us introduce you to the best psychics I Rei Rei Hotline" The Spirits and Such Consultation Office's official homepage...
The Spirits and Such Consultation
Office's official homepage...
"Available 24 hours! ~SpiSpi Call Center~" "[Psychics] Spirits and Such Consultation Office Homepage: Reigen Arataka [Exorcisms &
Séances]” "Psychic Jet I A relaxing spiritual life I Seasoning City Center” The Spirits and Such Consultation Office's official homepage...
"Available 24 hours! ~SpiSpi Call Center~" "[Psychics] Spirits and Such Consultation Office Homepage:
Reigen Arataka [Exorcisms & Séances]” "Psychic Jet I A relaxing spiritual life I Seasoning City Center”
To much surprise, it became quite popular,
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office" "The star psychic of the 21st century who defeated the
Dragger" "Welcome to Reigen Arataka's homepage!!" To much surprise, it became quite popular,
To much surprise, it became quite popular,
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office Official HP" "Hello, I'm Reigen Arataka, the new star of the psychic world ! Don't try to do it
alone. Come talk to me ! ! Honest billing and various courses available ! ! I" and a lot of requests for actual exorcisms started coming in.
And a lot of requests for actual exorcisms
started coming in.
"Those of you troubled with 'spiritual harm,* are they causing you trouble with your neighbors ! ?" "Do you
want to hear the voice of your loved one again...? and a lot of requests for actual exorcisms started coming in.
And a lot of requests for actual exorcisms
started coming in.
"Spirit Photography Evaluation" "Advice About Stigmatized Properties”
and a lot of requests for actual exorcisms started coming in.
And a lot of requests for actual exorcisms
started coming in.
"Your stiff shoulders may be due to a spirit on your back...” "Modern '"Urban
Legends'” and a lot of requests for actual exorcisms started coming in.
And a lot of requests for actual exorcisms
started coming in.
"Executing the Exorcism ! !" "Option A -- Trial Course"” "A Mere 2,000 yen" "Option B -- Serious Course” "A Mere 5,000 yen"
"Recommended” "Option C -- All-Out Course"” "A Mere 12,000 yen" and a lot of requests for actual exorcisms started coming in.
And a lot of requests for actual exorcisms
started coming in.
"Behold, Reigen Arataka's elegant special moves ! Salt Splash Banishing Salt Punch
Aroma Runaway Express” and a lot of requests for actual exorcisms started coming in.
And a lot of requests for actual exorcisms
started coming in.
"Essence of Life Draft"
"Low Carbs"
“Essence of Life Draft" "Low Carbs" But that
also meant that some of the requests coming in
But that also meant
that some of the requests coming in
were the kind that could never be taken on.
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
Coming down,
could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB.
Can't you feel your own frustration?
Coming down,
could you fill your satisfaction?
You're a MOB.
What do you want to be?
Wear your overflowing emotions
on your sleeve and break it down
What do you see once you go
beyond your limits?
(99.9! 99.9)
The mysterious percentage
Cr yin' my life, or yin' my psyche,
Cr yin' my heart in such commonplaces!
Is that your ideal? Is that your mind?
It all begins when it hits 100
The MOB is alive. The MOB is high.
The MOB is staying frustrated, aren't you?
Is that your ideal?
Is that your mind? Right now
YOUR LIFE IS YOUR OWN.
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
"Mob Psycho 100 II"
(Get ready, dig your anger up, MOB!)
(Get ready, wake your psyche up, MOB!)
(Get ready!)
"One Danger After Another
- Degeneration~"
Again...
No matter how many times you ask,
I'm not going to curse anyone for you.
Please leave.
But you're a psychic, right?
Come on, don't be such a spoilsport.
I'm begging you. Curse this guy for me.
I'm afraid I can't.
You can't be serious!
I traveled really far to come see you!
Nobody asked you to.
What?! Is that how you talk to a customer?!
Are they going to fight?
All right, all right! Fine, I'll do it.
Really?! I knew it'd be worth the trip!
"The Spiritual Compendium
17th Edition"
"The Spiritual Compendium 17th Edition"
But this is the only time I'm doing it.
And I won't be held responsible
for what happens.
Huh?
Keep this on your person at all times.
"Curse"
The hell is this?
It's a cursed, well, you know...
As long as you have that with you,
I'm sure something will happen someday.
Oh, I don't need any payment.
But just make sure you don't
tell anyone else about this.
I mean, I believe you,
but if you're messing with me...
...I'm going to curse you.
Man, he finally left.
I mean, I can understand hating someone
so much you want to curse them...
Do you have someone like that, too, Master?
Nope.
Do you?
Someone I want to curse?
Uh, you don't need to think
so hard about it.
Huh?
--Can't think of anyone.
--Don't take so long, then! You actually scared me!
Anyway, was it a good idea
to give him that thing?
Well, I just cooked it up on the spot.
I'm sure it won't harm anyone.
Do you really think so?
I mean...
Even if it's a lie,
". Goku NERO -"
". Goku NERO -" in his mind, he believes
that he's actually cursing someone.
In his mind, he believes that he's
actually cursing someone.
Is he going to keep living
under that impression?
Isn't that rather frightening?
Mob?
"The New Star of the 21st Century
Reigen Arataka"
"The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen Arataka”
That's rare... He's actually voicing his own opinion.
"The New Star of the 21st Century
Reigen Arataka"
Something's obviously bothering him.
Did I miss something?
Hello, this is Spirits and
Such Consultation Office.
This is the place.
At first, I thought it was a stalker,
so I talked to the police.
But it just didn't seem human...
It was staring at me through
the window the other day!
The window?
"Seasoning Moving Center"
We're on the fifth floor,
and there's no balcony... I see.
--You here, Dimple?
--The hell do you want?
Could you check things out
around this window?
See if there's a rope or something
dangling from the roof.
And why do I have to do this?
Feel free to eat any evil spirits you see.
Mob, do you sense anything?
Yes, though it's faint.
Nope, not a damn thing.
Why the hell did you close
the window, you jerk?!
But there definitely
seems to be a stalker...
What kind of interest would a ghost
have in a living woman?
Beats me. It's pretty rare for spirits
to have any sexual desires left.
It's not like they can reproduce anymore.
But does love always have to
come with sexual desires?
Actually, I don't want to
discuss this with you.
Right back at you, ya jerk.
Is this... a poltergeist?
What do I do? It must be mad
I called you here.
Did it settle down?
Outside the window!
I"'m S o r ry I Il m S o rry I
Mob! Vaporize it!
That's...
...a living person.
So it is a stalker!
Damn it! He disappeared!
He's in the next apartment.
Who are these people? Why are they here?
It's not like I did anything wrong.
I mean, yeah, I'm sorry I used an
out-of-body experience to spy on you.
But I seriously fell for you at first sight!
I've never felt like this before...
I didn't know what to do.
Y-Yeah... I'm serious about this.
I'm going to go out with her!
Don't get in my way! I'll murder you!
Why, you--
You pervy Peeping Tom!
Ow, ow, owie!
Say no to violence! Let me go!
I'll call the cops, you bastard!
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry! I was in the wrong!
I'll never do it again!
Please forgive me!
My feelings for you are genuine, though!
--So, please... p-p-p-p...
--You're seriously...
You're seriously insanely creepy!
I can't believe I was scared of that.
So he tried to hide his stalking tendencies
behind a supernatural phenomenon.
Don't try that at home, Shigeo.
Why?
Why does she feel so differently after finding
out it was a human and not an evil spirit?
I don't understand...
Man, he's got a lot on his mind today.
Guess I'll pick his brain later.
All right, let's head back
and grab some soba on the way.
Okay...
Oh, there he is!
We were waiting for you!
Hey, you sure got him working
a long part-time shift today.
Three jobs in one day?
That website is paying off.
We want to make some memories
before we graduate, man!
So, like, we want to go to some popular
haunted place and take a spirit photo.
But it'd suck if we actually
ran into an evil spirit.
So they're just messing around.
But it's not like I'm
going to turn them down.
When and where?
Right now, my dude!
We've got a car waiting just outside!
I doubt these guys have job offers lined up.
What happened to getting there
in 20 minutes? It's already been 30.
I think it might take another 30.
We might not have time for soba after all.
So who the heck are you? His assistant?
I'm a part-timer.
You work part-time at a psychic's office?
That's hilarious.
--How much do you--
--Mob!
Concentrate. Make sure you're
prepared for the unexpected.
--Right...
--Wow, you sound legit!
We're here.
Yo! This place is creepy AF!
OMG! I'm so excited!
--Holy shit, man.
--Holy shit.
You sense any spirits?
Faintly...
Doesn't deserve to be
a popular haunted spot, though.
All right, hurry up and
take that picture, please.
Got it!
I'm taking it!
Okay, say chee--
Actually, could you take it?
I want to vehemently decline,
but they're customers, so what can I do?
Okay, say chee--
Oh, hey, don't forget the flash!
Okay, say cheese.
We should head back.
My disciple's still in middle school.
Sure, thanks.
--TYVM.
--Thanks.
Also, regarding the fee...
What? Fee?
What are you even talking about?
What? The fee for this job.
Nothing bad happened, and you
didn't even do anything, psychic dude!
You really want us to pay you for nothing?
Isn't that a scam?
Yeah, like, a total scam!
No pay, and then...
Not even a ride back?
Yup. I'd say the unexpected just happened.
Oh, well. Let's head out to
the road and hail us a taxi.
No soba tonight.
"Mob Psycho 100 II"
Hey!
Hey, kid!
You ignoring me? Hey!
Look at you, stumbling around.
You're in our way.
But since you're here,
could you lend us some cash?
Huh? But I don't have any.
Why you freakin' out?
Could you bring us some money tomorrow, then?
--Huh?
--You heard the guy.
Uh, Sugimoto?
Hey, what's wrong?
Why are you stripping, Sugimoto?!
I'm an angel!
Sugimoto...
Dimple, stop! Stop that!
Sugimoto... Are you okay?
I dunno...
What just happened?
Let's try this again!
Hey, you little shit!
You were laughing just now, weren't you?
I-I wasn't!
Shut up! You get what this is, right?
We're mugging yo--
Sugimoto?!
I'm okay! Let him go, Ritsu.
You sure?
They seem like a bad crowd.
Dude, what's wrong with you, Sugimoto?
Did you need something from our club member?
Huh?
Wh-Who the hell are you guys?!
Who said you could surround
me like that, huh?
Bring it on, you bastards!
I'll kick yer asses!
Hey, stop squishing me, damn it!
Hey, I can't get out!
Hey!
Um, I'm fine, so please don't fight.
Fair enough.
Sugimoto!
You'll regret this, you jerks!
You sure you're all right?
Yes. Thank you.
You need to know when to
fight back, Kageyama.
Or they're just going to try
to bully you even more.
I can't think of a good way to.
Kick their asses with your
shadow leader powers.
You don't have to waste your powers
on guys like them, Nii-san.
If they show up again, I'll get rid of them.
Raking bad guys over the coals is
what's good for them and society.
Make sure you kick their
asses on your own next time.
You've got the power to do it.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
What? You ended up with a spirit photo?
Yes... So we wanted to
ask for your help again.
Just throw some salt around.
I don't do volunteer work.
We're really sorry! We'll pay!
So what's the job?
We want to go back to that haunted place
and have you make the ghost
in this picture disappear!
I mean, I can exorcise that
photograph if you'd like.
We don't even need to go back to the place.
No way! It's creepy enough
knowing that thing exists!
Please get rid of it!
So an exorcism request. Very well.
Let me explain the various options--
We'll take the most expensive one!
Looks like you got dragged out again.
And your Sunday got ruined yesterday.
You can get pissed off about this, y'know?
Please wrap this up as soon as possible.
There're three of them.
They don't seem to be evil spirits, though.
We'll just have to take care of them.
They're scaring our clients.
Go ahead and exorcise them.
Please don't.
The three of us are family.
We died in an accident and
lost our chance at a good life.
But now that we're ghosts,
we've been living here peacefully.
We haven't done anything wrong.
I just want... to stay with my
family a little bit longer.
As soon as this desire is fulfilled,
we will disappear naturally.
So I beg of you... Please, let us be.
Did you hear that, Master?
Nope, not a thing.
Their aura must be too weak.
Th-There's no reason to exorcise them.
They said that they
wouldn't do anything bad.
They're a family.
Hello?!
We called you here because we
need you to exorcise them!
It's way too creepy knowing they're here!
Who cares if they do anything bad or not?
Not to mention, we said we'd pay you!
Hurry up and exorcise them already!
I'm getting goosebumps just standing here!
It's so creepy,
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
What's the matter, Mob?
You've gotten rid of plenty
of evil spirits before.
These people just want to live in peace.
I can't... I don't want to destroy that.
Just hurry up and do it already!
No one cares how you feel!
Sir, we asked for your help
because we really needed it.
Our customers always take top priority.
However, if spirits deserve
as much respect as the living,
and the three here are truly
just a family living peacefully...
Then I can't make Mob do something as
heinous as barging in and dispatching them.
But our clients' fear is real, too.
What should I do?
As a professional, can I really put
the ghosts above the clients?
Hey, man of the house.
I see you've got plenty of
pent-up spiritual power.
Dimple?
You gained that strength to
protect your family, right?
In that case...
Why not kill those three right now?
They won't have to exorcise you
if the clients are dead.
You want to live peacefully
with your family, right?
Go on. What other choice do you have?
Darling...
Daddy...
I beg of you... Please let us be.
I cannot do something so horrific,
especially in front of my child...
I see. Well, what're you gonna do, then?
But we have nowhere left to run.
If you must go through with it,
we'll just have to accept it.
But, please...
Please, I ask that you
let us all go together,
wherever it may be.
Mob, are the spirits still saying something?
--You...
--Hey... So what's going on?
A moment, please.
What's wrong, Mob?
He's so against exorcising them
that it's making him tremble.
That much, huh?
Okay, got it. Let's skip the exorcism.
It's not like I'm ordering you.
It's okay to listen to your feelings.
Yup. You don't have to
take this so seriously.
You're plenty strong, Shigeo.
I don't think you understand...
This must be something
that only I understand...
I mean, there's no way I can
go off my feelings alone.
I can't take this lightly.
If I truly decide to protect this family,
that'll mean the clients will
have to get hurt instead.
How long is this gonna take, damn it?!
Who cares what the brat--
Yo, what the hell is this? Salt?!
This concludes the exorcism.
What? Wait, seriously?
That was it?
We're done here.
Uh, okay.
Reigen? What's the matter with you now?
So that's what's going on here...
Why didn't I realize it sooner?
He can do so much more
than an average person.
The world he can see
is far bigger than ours.
Curses and spirits are
a part of Mob's daily life.
Both the human and the inhuman
are equally close to him.
Damn it!
It's all because I took too many jobs,
got complacent, and half-assed things.
Let's head back.
Want some soba?
Okay.
"Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
You okay with that?
You actually took money for just
throwing a bunch of salt around.
"The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen Arataka Spirits and Such Consultation
Office" You actually took money for just throwing a bunch of salt around.
"The New Star of the 21st Century Reigen
Arataka Spirits and Such Consultation Office"
What was I supposed to do?
If I hadn't taken the money,
it would've been suspicious.
More importantly, you're sure
they weren't evil spirits, right?
"If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism
fee on 1 of them will be on the house!!"
“If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism fee on 1 of them will be on the
house!! Yeah. I tried to provoke him, but he didn't turn into an evil spirit.
Yeah. I tried to provoke him,
but he didn't turn into an evil spirit.
“If there are 3 evil spirits, the exorcism fee on 1 of them will be on the
house!! Yeah. I tried to provoke him, but he didn't turn into an evil spirit.
Yeah. I tried to provoke him,
but he didn't turn into an evil spirit.
Why are you trembling now?
Oh, you're yawning.
Man, you two are like night and day.
Hey, you've got something on your back.
What?
Yeah, someone definitely cursed you.
What'll happen to me if I leave it alone?
You might slip on a banana peel at least.
That'd be enough to do me in
if I was on some stairs.
--Get rid of it for me.
--Your attitude sucks, so nope.
Please, I can't ask Mob to do this for me.
I bet the guy from yesterday hired
someone who could actually use curses.
All right, fine.
He might be able to see
something more terrifying
than anything that we can ever witness.
The things he feared,
and the things he avoided...
Mob understood that they
were different from the norm.
"Shampoo" Mob understood that
they were different from the norm.
Mob understood that they
were different from the norm.
If I ever end up wanting to curse someone...
If I ever end up using my powers for evil...
If I ever end up wanting to
eradicate people rather than spirits...
I wonder if there will be anyone to stop me.
Mob tried to think about everything
that happened over the past two days,
but perhaps out of exhaustion,
he immediately fell asleep.
"Mob 67%"
I spilled a seed and lost sight of it
I'll find it using the color it's dyed in
and watch it grow
It immediately returned
to the palm of my hand
But it's still too light and too frail
to reach for the skies
The world coldly drains away all the heat
The bright sunshine just isn't enough
The memories are closing off what lies ahead
Shake off their warmth
and set off into the distance
If I let it wither, it'd be over just like that
But my hope just doesn't fade away
We've been invited to a rich guy's house!
I smell a huge score!
We're gonna make that money, Mob!
Next time on Mob Psycho 100 Il Episode 4:
"Inside
- Evil Spirit~."
A streaming service? But of course,
that's an excellent decision!
"Inside - Evil Spirit~" A streaming service?
But of course, that's an excellent decision!